[{"date":"Sun, 13 Jun 2021 18:54:52 -0400","score":2,"shortened date":"13\/06\/2021 18:54:52","questions":[{"number":1,"question":"Swimwear is acceptable attire for FBLA conferences.","answer":["false"],"correct":"true","user answer":["false"]},{"number":2,"question":"Match the following officer roles to their responsibilities in FBLA","answer":["President : preside over all meetings","Secretary : keep an accurate membership and attendance roll","Treasurer : receive and act as custodian of chapter funds"],"correct":"false","user answer":["President : keep an accurate membership and attendance roll","Secretary : null","Treasurer : null"]},{"number":3,"question":"For competitive events in which it is required, according to the FBLA Format Guide, which of the following are acceptable fonts?","answer":["Arial","Calibri","Times New Roman"],"correct":"true","user answer":["Times New Roman","Calibri","Arial"]},{"number":4,"question":"What is the first line of the FBLA creed?","answer":["I believe education is the right of every person"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":5,"question":"What is the membership theme of FBLA for the 2020-2021 year?","answer":["aspire"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]}],"time":15},{"date":"Sun, 13 Jun 2021 16:24:22 -0400","score":0,"shortened date":"13\/06\/2021 16:24:22","questions":[{"number":1,"question":"Match the following people to their importance within FBLA","answer":["Dorothy L. Travis : who the Parliamentary Procedure Event is named after","Hollis and Kitty Guy : who the Gold Seal Award of Merit is named after","Jean Buckley : former president of the national FBLA-PBL office"],"correct":"false","user answer":["Dorothy L. Travis : No answer","Hollis and Kitty Guy : No answer","Jean Buckley : No answer"]},{"number":2,"question":"Where was the concept of FBLA developed?","answer":["Columbia University"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":3,"question":"Swimwear is acceptable attire for FBLA conferences.","answer":["false"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":4,"question":"Which of the following are NOT types of Competitive Events under FBLA?","answer":["Essay Writings","Performing Arts Events"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":5,"question":"What Greek letter does the P in FBLA-PBL stand for?","answer":["phi"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]}],"time":3},{"date":"Tue, 25 May 2021 19:31:13 -0400","score":4,"shortened date":"25\/05\/2021 19:31:13","questions":[{"number":1,"question":"Swimwear is acceptable attire for FBLA conferences.","answer":["false"],"correct":"true","user answer":["false"]},{"number":2,"question":"How many winners are there for the National Technical Honor Society Scholarship?","answer":["2"],"correct":"true","user answer":["2"]},{"number":3,"question":"Which of the following are official colors of FBLA?","answer":["Blue","Gold"],"correct":"true","user answer":["Gold","Blue"]},{"number":4,"question":"What is the two-day seminar that is held in conjunction with the National Leadership Conference by FBLA?","answer":["Institute for Leaders"],"correct":"true","user answer":["Institute for Leaders"]},{"number":5,"question":"Match the following scholarships FBLA helps to offer with their respective winnings","answer":["FBLA Distinguished Business Leader Scholarship : $500 per winner","Johnson & Wales University Scholarship : up to full tuition for winners","National Technical Honor Society Scholarship : $1,000 per winner"],"correct":"false","user answer":["FBLA Distinguished Business Leader Scholarship : $1,000 per winner","Johnson & Wales University Scholarship : up to full tuition for winners","National Technical Honor Society Scholarship : $500 per winner"]}],"time":27},{"date":"Tue, 25 May 2021 16:16:14 -0400","score":0,"shortened date":"25\/05\/2021 16:16:14","questions":[{"number":1,"question":"Match the following dates to their importance","answer":["November 15 : American Enterprise Day","November 17 : March of Dimes World Prematurity Day","March 1 : Date by which dues must be received for competition eligibility"],"correct":"false","user answer":["November 15 : No answer","November 17 : No answer","March 1 : No answer"]},{"number":2,"question":"FBLA has an international presence in China.","answer":["true"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":3,"question":"What is the two-day seminar that is held in conjunction with the National Leadership Conference by FBLA?","answer":["Institute for Leaders"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":4,"question":"In what year was the idea of FBLA first thought of?","answer":["1937"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":5,"question":"For competitive events in which it is required, according to the FBLA Format Guide, which of the following are acceptable fonts?","answer":["Arial","Calibri","Times New Roman"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]}],"time":3},{"date":"Wed, 17 Mar 2021 22:04:37 -0400","score":3,"shortened date":"17\/03\/2021 22:04:37","questions":[{"number":1,"question":"How many voting delegates can a local FBLA chapter of 40 members send to the National Leadership Conference?","answer":["2"],"correct":"false","user answer":["39"]},{"number":2,"question":"Which of the following are conferences which FBLA conducts?","answer":["National Leadership Conference","National Fall Leadership Conference"],"correct":"true","user answer":["National Fall Leadership Conference","National Leadership Conference"]},{"number":3,"question":"Where was the concept of FBLA developed?","answer":["Columbia University"],"correct":"true","user answer":["Columbia University"]},{"number":4,"question":"Match the following people to their importance within FBLA","answer":["Dorothy L. Travis : who the Parliamentary Procedure Event is named after","Hollis and Kitty Guy : who the Gold Seal Award of Merit is named after","Jean Buckley : former president of the national FBLA-PBL office"],"correct":"false","user answer":["Dorothy L. Travis : former president of the national FBLA-PBL office","Hollis and Kitty Guy : who the Gold Seal Award of Merit is named after","Jean Buckley : who the Parliamentary Procedure Event is named after"]},{"number":5,"question":"FBLA has an international presence in Vietnam.","answer":["false"],"correct":"true","user answer":["false"]}],"time":110},{"date":"Tue, 16 Mar 2021 07:59:22 -0400","score":4,"shortened date":"16\/03\/2021 07:59:22","questions":[{"number":1,"question":"Where is FBLA currently headquartered?","answer":["Reston, Virginia"],"correct":"true","user answer":["Reston, Virginia"]},{"number":2,"question":"Which of the following are conferences which FBLA conducts?","answer":["National Leadership Conference","National Fall Leadership Conference"],"correct":"false","user answer":["National Leadership Conference"]},{"number":3,"question":"Match the following FBLA divisions to their respective school levels","answer":["FBLA : High School","FBLA-ML : Middle School","PBL : College"],"correct":"true","user answer":["FBLA : High School","FBLA-ML : Middle School","PBL : College"]},{"number":4,"question":"In which month, every year, is the National FBLA-PBL Week?","answer":["February"],"correct":"true","user answer":["February"]},{"number":5,"question":"A hat is considered appropriate attire for FBLA conferences.","answer":["false"],"correct":"true","user answer":["false"]}],"time":181},{"date":"Mon, 15 Mar 2021 23:40:56 -0400","score":4,"shortened date":"15\/03\/2021 23:40:56","questions":[{"number":1,"question":"Which of the following are the core activities on which all levels of the Business Achievement Awards are based off of, as outlined by FBLA?","answer":["Service","Education","Progress"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":2,"question":"Match the following months to their respective events or importance","answer":["February : National FBLA-PBL Week","November : Prematurity Awareness Month","October : National Fall Leadership Conference"],"correct":"false","user answer":["February : No answer","November : No answer","October : No answer"]},{"number":3,"question":"The PBL part of FBLA-PBL is an acronym representing Greek letters.","answer":["true"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":4,"question":"What Greek letter does the P in FBLA-PBL stand for?","answer":["phi"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":5,"question":"Where was the concept of FBLA developed?","answer":["Columbia University"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]}],"time":3},{"date":"Mon, 15 Mar 2021 13:25:00 -0400","score":5,"shortened date":"15\/03\/2021 13:25:00","questions":[{"number":1,"question":"Match the following levels of the FBLA Business Achievement Awards to when they would be presented to their respective winners","answer":["Future : Presented at a local awards ceremony or FBLA event by advisor","Leader : Presented at State Leadership Conference","America : Presented at National Leadership Conference"],"correct":"false","user answer":["Future : No answer","Leader : No answer","America : No answer"]},{"number":2,"question":"How many goals have the FBLA-PBL explicitly outlined for the organization?","answer":["9"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":3,"question":"Which of the following FBLA administrative regions includes non-US chapters?","answer":["Eastern"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":4,"question":"The FBLA National Center mortgage was retired in 2010.","answer":["false"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":5,"question":"Which of the following are NOT types of Competitive Events under FBLA?","answer":["Essay Writings","Performing Arts Events"],"correct":"true","user answer":["Performing Arts Events","Essay Writings"]}],"time":8},{"date":"Sun, 14 Mar 2021 20:01:23 -0400","score":4,"shortened date":"14\/03\/2021 20:01:23","questions":[{"number":1,"question":"Match the following levels of the FBLA Business Achievement Awards to when they would be presented to their respective winners","answer":["Future : Presented at a local awards ceremony or FBLA event by advisor","Leader : Presented at State Leadership Conference","America : Presented at National Leadership Conference"],"correct":"false","user answer":["Future : No answer","Leader : No answer","America : No answer"]},{"number":2,"question":"FBLA is the largest career student business organization in the world.","answer":["true"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":3,"question":"Which of the following are official colors of FBLA?","answer":["Blue","Gold"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":4,"question":"What is the minimum number of members required for an FBLA chapter?","answer":["5"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":5,"question":"Which of the following FBLA administrative regions includes non-US chapters?","answer":["Eastern"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]}],"time":2},{"date":"Sun, 14 Mar 2021 19:58:33 -0400","score":4,"shortened date":"14\/03\/2021 20:01:33","questions":[{"number":1,"question":"What is the first line of the FBLA creed?","answer":["I believe education is the right of every person"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":2,"question":"A collared dress shirt with a necktie is acceptable attire for FBLA conferences.","answer":["true"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":3,"question":"What Greek letter does the P in FBLA-PBL stand for?","answer":["phi"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":4,"question":"Match the following people to their importance within FBLA","answer":["Dorothy L. Travis : who the Parliamentary Procedure Event is named after","Hollis and Kitty Guy : who the Gold Seal Award of Merit is named after","Jean Buckley : former president of the national FBLA-PBL office"],"correct":"false","user answer":["Dorothy L. Travis : No answer","Hollis and Kitty Guy : No answer","Jean Buckley : No answer"]},{"number":5,"question":"Which of the following are NOT types of Competitive Events under FBLA?","answer":["Essay Writings","Performing Arts Events"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]}],"time":2},{"date":"Sun, 14 Mar 2021 19:51:28 -0400","score":3,"shortened date":"14\/03\/2021 19:51:28","questions":[{"number":1,"question":"Match the following FBLA Chapter programs to each of their respective focus","answer":["Super Sweeps : recruitment and retention","Non-Stop November : membership involvement","Action Awareness : FBLA awareness"],"correct":"false","user answer":["Super Sweeps : No answer","Non-Stop November : No answer","Action Awareness : No answer"]},{"number":2,"question":"In which U.S. state was the first FBLA state chapter established?","answer":["Iowa"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":3,"question":"FBLA has an international presence in China.","answer":["true"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":4,"question":"What is the first line of the FBLA creed?","answer":["I believe education is the right of every person"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":5,"question":"Which of the following are official colors of FBLA?","answer":["Blue","Gold"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]}],"time":2},{"date":"Sat, 13 Mar 2021 23:22:36 -0400","score":5,"shortened date":"13\/03\/2021 23:22:36","questions":[{"number":1,"question":"What is the two-day seminar that is held in conjunction with the National Leadership Conference by FBLA?","answer":["Institute for Leaders"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":2,"question":"Swimwear is acceptable attire for FBLA conferences.","answer":["false"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":3,"question":"Which of the following are NOT types of Competitive Events under FBLA?","answer":["Essay Writings","Performing Arts Events"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":4,"question":"Match the following FBLA divisions to their respective school levels","answer":["FBLA : High School","FBLA-ML : Middle School","PBL : College"],"correct":"false","user answer":["FBLA : No answer","FBLA-ML : No answer","PBL : No answer"]},{"number":5,"question":"What is the membership theme of FBLA for the 2020-2021 year?","answer":["aspire"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]}],"time":10},{"date":"Fri, 12 Mar 2021 20:06:09 -0400","score":3,"shortened date":"12\/03\/2021 20:06:09","questions":[{"number":1,"question":"Which of the following are NOT official FBLA fundraising partners?","answer":["Chipotle","Sam\u2019s Club","Baja Fresh"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":2,"question":"Where was the concept of FBLA developed?","answer":["Columbia University"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":3,"question":"Match the following FBLA divisions to their respective school levels","answer":["FBLA : High School","FBLA-ML : Middle School","PBL : College"],"correct":"false","user answer":["FBLA : No answer","FBLA-ML : No answer","PBL : No answer"]},{"number":4,"question":"How many goals have the FBLA-PBL explicitly outlined for the organization?","answer":["9"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":5,"question":"FBLA is the largest career student business organization in the world.","answer":["true"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]}],"time":3},{"date":"Wed, 10 Mar 2021 12:06:03 -0400","score":3,"shortened date":"10\/03\/2021 12:06:03","questions":[{"number":1,"question":"What is the flagship publication for FBLA and FBLA-Middle Level students and advisers?","answer":["Tomorrow\u2019s Business Leader"],"correct":"true","user answer":["Tomorrow\u2019s Business Leader"]},{"number":2,"question":"Which of the following are NOT types of Competitive Events under FBLA?","answer":["Essay Writings","Performing Arts Events"],"correct":"true","user answer":["Essay Writings","Performing Arts Events"]},{"number":3,"question":"Match the following scholarships FBLA helps to offer with their respective winnings","answer":["FBLA Distinguished Business Leader Scholarship : $500 per winner","Johnson & Wales University Scholarship : up to full tuition for winners","National Technical Honor Society Scholarship : $1,000 per winner"],"correct":"false","user answer":["FBLA Distinguished Business Leader Scholarship : No answer","Johnson & Wales University Scholarship : No answer","National Technical Honor Society Scholarship : No answer"]},{"number":4,"question":"The FBLA National Center mortgage was retired in 2010.","answer":["false"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":5,"question":"How many national officers are there in FBLA?","answer":["9"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]}],"time":11},{"date":"Mon, 8 Mar 2021 20:05:40 -0400","score":3,"shortened date":"08\/03\/2021 20:05:40","questions":[{"number":1,"question":"Match the following officer roles to their responsibilities in FBLA","answer":["President : preside over all meetings","Secretary : keep an accurate membership and attendance roll","Treasurer : receive and act as custodian of chapter funds"],"correct":"true","user answer":["President : preside over all meetings","Secretary : keep an accurate membership and attendance roll","Treasurer : receive and act as custodian of chapter funds"]},{"number":2,"question":"Where was the concept of FBLA developed?","answer":["Columbia University"],"correct":"true","user answer":["Columbia University"]},{"number":3,"question":"Which of the following are the core activities on which all levels of the Business Achievement Awards are based off of, as outlined by FBLA?","answer":["Service","Education","Progress"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":4,"question":"How many national officers are there in FBLA?","answer":["9"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":5,"question":"FBLA sells bow ties as a part of its official merchandise.","answer":["true"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]}],"time":12},{"date":"Fri, 5 Mar 2021 20:05:25 -0400","score":3,"shortened date":"05\/03\/2021 20:05:25","questions":[{"number":1,"question":"Who is credited as the founder of FBLA?","answer":["Hamden L. Forkner"],"correct":"true","user answer":["Hamden L. Forkner"]},{"number":2,"question":"FBLA is the largest career student business organization in the world.","answer":["true"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":3,"question":"What is the minimum number of members required for an FBLA chapter?","answer":["5"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":4,"question":"For competitive events in which it is required, according to the FBLA Format Guide, which of the following are acceptable fonts?","answer":["Arial","Calibri","Times New Roman"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":5,"question":"Match the following dates to their importance","answer":["November 15 : American Enterprise Day","November 17 : March of Dimes World Prematurity Day","March 1 : Date by which dues must be received for competition eligibility"],"correct":"false","user answer":["November 15 : No answer","November 17 : No answer","March 1 : No answer"]}],"time":3},{"date":"Mon, 1 Mar 2021 20:05:18 -0400","score":1,"shortened date":"01\/03\/2021 20:05:18","questions":[{"number":1,"question":"Match the following people to their importance within FBLA","answer":["Dorothy L. Travis : who the Parliamentary Procedure Event is named after","Hollis and Kitty Guy : who the Gold Seal Award of Merit is named after","Jean Buckley : former president of the national FBLA-PBL office"],"correct":"false","user answer":["Dorothy L. Travis : No answer","Hollis and Kitty Guy : No answer","Jean Buckley : No answer"]},{"number":2,"question":"What is the first line of the FBLA creed?","answer":["I believe education is the right of every person"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":3,"question":"How many winners are there for the National Technical Honor Society Scholarship?","answer":["2"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":4,"question":"Which of the following are words on the FBLA-PBL Crest?","answer":["Service","Education","Progress"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":5,"question":"Swimwear is acceptable attire for FBLA conferences.","answer":["false"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]}],"time":3},{"date":"Sun, 28 Feb 2021 11:05:12 -0400","score":2,"shortened date":"28\/02\/2021 11:05:12","questions":[{"number":1,"question":"Jean Buckley is the current president of the FBLA national association.","answer":["false"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":2,"question":"Match the following months to their respective events or importance","answer":["February : National FBLA-PBL Week","November : Prematurity Awareness Month","October : National Fall Leadership Conference"],"correct":"false","user answer":["February : No answer","November : No answer","October : No answer"]},{"number":3,"question":"What is the minimum number of members required for an FBLA chapter?","answer":["5"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":4,"question":"For competitive events in which it is required, according to the FBLA Format Guide, which of the following are acceptable fonts?","answer":["Arial","Calibri","Times New Roman"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":5,"question":"What is the first line of the FBLA Code of Ethics?","answer":["I will be honest and sincere"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]}],"time":2},{"date":"Sat, 27 Feb 2021 20:05:07 -0400","score":2,"shortened date":"27\/02\/2021 20:05:07","questions":[{"number":1,"question":"Which of the following FBLA administrative regions includes non-US chapters?","answer":["Eastern"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":2,"question":"Which of the following are official colors of FBLA?","answer":["Blue","Gold"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":3,"question":"What is the minimum number of members required for an FBLA chapter?","answer":["5"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":4,"question":"Match the following dates to their importance","answer":["November 15 : American Enterprise Day","November 17 : March of Dimes World Prematurity Day","March 1 : Date by which dues must be received for competition eligibility"],"correct":"false","user answer":["November 15 : No answer","November 17 : No answer","March 1 : No answer"]},{"number":5,"question":"The FBLA National Center mortgage was retired in 2010.","answer":["false"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]}],"time":2},{"date":"Wed, 24 Feb 2021 12:05:01 -0400","score":1,"shortened date":"24\/02\/2021 12:05:01","questions":[{"number":1,"question":"Jean Buckley is the current president of the FBLA national association.","answer":["false"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":2,"question":"How many FBLA administrative regions are there?","answer":["5"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":3,"question":"In what year was the first high school FBLA chapter chartered?","answer":["1942"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":4,"question":"Which of the following are NOT types of Competitive Events under FBLA?","answer":["Essay Writings","Performing Arts Events"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":5,"question":"Match the following FBLA Chapter programs to each of their respective focus","answer":["Super Sweeps : recruitment and retention","Non-Stop November : membership involvement","Action Awareness : FBLA awareness"],"correct":"false","user answer":["Super Sweeps : No answer","Non-Stop November : No answer","Action Awareness : No answer"]}],"time":2},{"date":"Mon, 22 Feb 2021 16:14:56 -0400","score":3,"shortened date":"22\/02\/2021 16:14:56","questions":[{"number":1,"question":"How many FBLA administrative regions are there?","answer":["5"],"correct":"false","user answer":["9"]},{"number":2,"question":"What was the Professional Division of FBLA originally called?","answer":["Alumni Division"],"correct":"true","user answer":["Alumni Division"]},{"number":3,"question":"Jean Buckley is the current president of the FBLA national association.","answer":["false"],"correct":"true","user answer":["false"]},{"number":4,"question":"Which of the following are the core activities on which all levels of the Business Achievement Awards are based off of, as outlined by FBLA?","answer":["Service","Education","Progress"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":5,"question":"Match the following FBLA divisions to their respective school levels","answer":["FBLA : High School","FBLA-ML : Middle School","PBL : College"],"correct":"true","user answer":["FBLA : High School","FBLA-ML : Middle School","PBL : College"]}],"time":19},{"date":"Fri, 19 Feb 2021 10:26:17 -0400","score":2,"shortened date":"19\/02\/2021 10:26:17","questions":[{"number":1,"question":"What is the first line of the FBLA creed?","answer":["I believe education is the right of every person"],"correct":"true","user answer":["I believe education is the right of every person"]},{"number":2,"question":"Which of the following are real administrative regions within FBLA?","answer":["Mountain Plains","Western"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":3,"question":"Match the following officer roles to their responsibilities in FBLA","answer":["President : preside over all meetings","Secretary : keep an accurate membership and attendance roll","Treasurer : receive and act as custodian of chapter funds"],"correct":"false","user answer":["President : No answer","Secretary : No answer","Treasurer : No answer"]},{"number":4,"question":"How many winners are there for the National Technical Honor Society Scholarship?","answer":["2"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":5,"question":"Jean Buckley is the current president of the FBLA national association.","answer":["false"],"correct":"true","user answer":["false"]}],"time":8},{"date":"Wed, 17 Feb 2021 20:04:06 -0400","score":2,"shortened date":"17\/02\/2021 20:04:06","questions":[{"number":1,"question":"FBLA sells bow ties as a part of its official merchandise.","answer":["true"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":2,"question":"Match the following officer roles to their responsibilities in FBLA","answer":["President : preside over all meetings","Secretary : keep an accurate membership and attendance roll","Treasurer : receive and act as custodian of chapter funds"],"correct":"false","user answer":["President : No answer","Secretary : No answer","Treasurer : No answer"]},{"number":3,"question":"Which of the following are the core activities on which all levels of the Business Achievement Awards are based off of, as outlined by FBLA?","answer":["Service","Education","Progress"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":4,"question":"What is the flagship publication for FBLA and FBLA-Middle Level students and advisers?","answer":["Tomorrow\u2019s Business Leader"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":5,"question":"How many different articles are there in the FBLA Bylaws?","answer":["13"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]}],"time":2},{"date":"Wed, 17 Feb 2021 19:04:00 -0400","score":2,"shortened date":"17\/02\/2021 19:04:00","questions":[{"number":1,"question":"Which of the following are objective tests in FBLA?","answer":["Business Communications","Sports & Entertainment Management","Personal Finance"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":2,"question":"Match the following scholarships FBLA helps to offer with their respective winnings","answer":["FBLA Distinguished Business Leader Scholarship : $500 per winner","Johnson & Wales University Scholarship : up to full tuition for winners","National Technical Honor Society Scholarship : $1,000 per winner"],"correct":"false","user answer":["FBLA Distinguished Business Leader Scholarship : No answer","Johnson & Wales University Scholarship : No answer","National Technical Honor Society Scholarship : No answer"]},{"number":3,"question":"How many FBLA administrative regions are there?","answer":["5"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":4,"question":"FBLA sells bow ties as a part of its official merchandise.","answer":["true"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":5,"question":"Where is FBLA currently headquartered?","answer":["Reston, Virginia"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]}],"time":2},{"date":"Wed, 17 Feb 2021 19:00:56 -0400","score":2,"shortened date":"17\/02\/2021 19:00:56","questions":[{"number":1,"question":"What is the first line of the FBLA Code of Ethics?","answer":["I will be honest and sincere"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":2,"question":"Which of the following are guidelines listed by the FBLA for social networking on behalf of FBLA chapters?","answer":["Be Secure","Be Responsible","Be Transparent","Be Fair"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":3,"question":"How many goals have the FBLA-PBL explicitly outlined for the organization?","answer":["9"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":4,"question":"FBLA sells bow ties as a part of its official merchandise.","answer":["true"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":5,"question":"Match the following scholarships FBLA helps to offer with their respective winnings","answer":["FBLA Distinguished Business Leader Scholarship : $500 per winner","Johnson & Wales University Scholarship : up to full tuition for winners","National Technical Honor Society Scholarship : $1,000 per winner"],"correct":"false","user answer":["FBLA Distinguished Business Leader Scholarship : No answer","Johnson & Wales University Scholarship : No answer","National Technical Honor Society Scholarship : No answer"]}],"time":3},{"date":"Tue, 16 Feb 2021 20:03:48 -0400","score":1,"shortened date":"16\/02\/2021 20:03:48","questions":[{"number":1,"question":"Match the following people to their importance within FBLA","answer":["Dorothy L. Travis : who the Parliamentary Procedure Event is named after","Hollis and Kitty Guy : who the Gold Seal Award of Merit is named after","Jean Buckley : former president of the national FBLA-PBL office"],"correct":"false","user answer":["Dorothy L. Travis : No answer","Hollis and Kitty Guy : No answer","Jean Buckley : No answer"]},{"number":2,"question":"FBLA sells bow ties as a part of its official merchandise.","answer":["true"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":3,"question":"For competitive events in which it is required, according to the FBLA Format Guide, which of the following are acceptable fonts?","answer":["Arial","Calibri","Times New Roman"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":4,"question":"What is the minimum number of members required for an FBLA chapter?","answer":["5"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":5,"question":"Who is credited as the founder of FBLA?","answer":["Hamden L. Forkner"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]}],"time":3},{"date":"Mon, 15 Feb 2021 15:19:38 -0400","score":2,"shortened date":"15\/02\/2021 15:19:38","questions":[{"number":1,"question":"Match the following FBLA Chapter programs to each of their respective focus","answer":["Super Sweeps : recruitment and retention","Non-Stop November : membership involvement","Action Awareness : FBLA awareness"],"correct":"false","user answer":["Super Sweeps : No answer","Non-Stop November : No answer","Action Awareness : No answer"]},{"number":2,"question":"The PBL part of FBLA-PBL is an acronym representing Greek letters.","answer":["true"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":3,"question":"Which of the following FBLA administrative regions includes non-US chapters?","answer":["Eastern"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":4,"question":"Which of the following are the core activities on which all levels of the Business Achievement Awards are based off of, as outlined by FBLA?","answer":["Service","Education","Progress"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":5,"question":"How many voting delegates can a local FBLA chapter of 40 members send to the National Leadership Conference?","answer":["2"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]}],"time":2},{"date":"Mon, 15 Feb 2021 10:03:32 -0400","score":2,"shortened date":"15\/02\/2021 10:03:32","questions":[{"number":1,"question":"How many winners are there for the National Technical Honor Society Scholarship?","answer":["2"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":2,"question":"Which of the following are NOT levels of the FBLA Business Achievement Awards?","answer":["Entrepreneur","Pioneer"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":3,"question":"What is the first line of the FBLA creed?","answer":["I believe education is the right of every person"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":4,"question":"Match the following FBLA divisions to their respective founding year","answer":["FBLA-ML : formed in 1994","PBL : formed in 1958","PD : formed in 1979"],"correct":"false","user answer":["FBLA-ML : No answer","PBL : No answer","PD : No answer"]},{"number":5,"question":"Swimwear is acceptable attire for FBLA conferences.","answer":["false"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]}],"time":2},{"date":"Mon, 15 Feb 2021 10:00:32 -0400","score":2,"shortened date":"15\/02\/2021 10:00:26","questions":[{"number":1,"question":"Which of the following are official colors of FBLA?","answer":["Blue","Gold"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":2,"question":"In what year was the first high school FBLA chapter chartered?","answer":["1942"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":3,"question":"In which month, every year, is the National FBLA-PBL Week?","answer":["February"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":4,"question":"Match the following FBLA divisions to their respective founding year","answer":["FBLA-ML : formed in 1994","PBL : formed in 1958","PD : formed in 1979"],"correct":"false","user answer":["FBLA-ML : No answer","PBL : No answer","PD : No answer"]},{"number":5,"question":"A hat is considered appropriate attire for FBLA conferences.","answer":["false"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]}],"time":2},{"date":"Sun, 14 Feb 2021 20:03:21 -0400","score":1,"shortened date":"14\/02\/2021 20:03:21","questions":[{"number":1,"question":"How many voting delegates can a local FBLA chapter of 40 members send to the National Leadership Conference?","answer":["2"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":2,"question":"Where was the concept of FBLA developed?","answer":["Columbia University"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":3,"question":"Swimwear is acceptable attire for FBLA conferences.","answer":["false"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":4,"question":"Match the following FBLA divisions to their respective school levels","answer":["FBLA : High School","FBLA-ML : Middle School","PBL : College"],"correct":"false","user answer":["FBLA : No answer","FBLA-ML : No answer","PBL : No answer"]},{"number":5,"question":"Which of the following are objective tests in FBLA?","answer":["Business Communications","Sports & Entertainment Management","Personal Finance"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]}],"time":2},{"date":"Sun, 14 Feb 2021 16:03:14 -0400","score":2,"shortened date":"14\/02\/2021 16:03:14","questions":[{"number":1,"question":"Match the following people to their importance within FBLA","answer":["Dorothy L. Travis : who the Parliamentary Procedure Event is named after","Hollis and Kitty Guy : who the Gold Seal Award of Merit is named after","Jean Buckley : former president of the national FBLA-PBL office"],"correct":"false","user answer":["Dorothy L. Travis : No answer","Hollis and Kitty Guy : No answer","Jean Buckley : No answer"]},{"number":2,"question":"Who is credited as the founder of FBLA?","answer":["Hamden L. Forkner"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":3,"question":"FBLA sells bow ties as a part of its official merchandise.","answer":["true"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":4,"question":"Which of the following are conferences which FBLA conducts?","answer":["National Leadership Conference","National Fall Leadership Conference"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":5,"question":"In which U.S. state was the first FBLA state chapter established?","answer":["Iowa"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]}],"time":2},{"date":"Sun, 14 Feb 2021 16:00:09 -0400","score":0,"shortened date":"14\/02\/2021 16:00:09","questions":[{"number":1,"question":"Match the following people to their importance within FBLA","answer":["Dorothy L. Travis : who the Parliamentary Procedure Event is named after","Hollis and Kitty Guy : who the Gold Seal Award of Merit is named after","Jean Buckley : former president of the national FBLA-PBL office"],"correct":"false","user answer":["Dorothy L. Travis : No answer","Hollis and Kitty Guy : No answer","Jean Buckley : No answer"]},{"number":2,"question":"The PBL part of FBLA-PBL is an acronym representing Greek letters.","answer":["true"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":3,"question":"In what year was the idea of FBLA first thought of?","answer":["1937"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":4,"question":"Who is credited as the founder of FBLA?","answer":["Hamden L. Forkner"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":5,"question":"Which of the following are NOT official FBLA fundraising partners?","answer":["Chipotle","Sam\u2019s Club","Baja Fresh"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]}],"time":2},{"date":"Sun, 14 Feb 2021 15:56:03 -0400","score":1,"shortened date":"14\/02\/2021 15:56:03","questions":[{"number":1,"question":"What was the Professional Division of FBLA originally called?","answer":["Alumni Division"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":2,"question":"A collared dress shirt with a necktie is acceptable attire for FBLA conferences.","answer":["true"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":3,"question":"What Greek letter does the P in FBLA-PBL stand for?","answer":["phi"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":4,"question":"Which of the following are NOT official FBLA fundraising partners?","answer":["Chipotle","Sam\u2019s Club","Baja Fresh"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":5,"question":"Match the following FBLA divisions to their respective founding year","answer":["FBLA-ML : formed in 1994","PBL : formed in 1958","PD : formed in 1979"],"correct":"false","user answer":["FBLA-ML : No answer","PBL : No answer","PD : No answer"]}],"time":2},{"date":"Sun, 14 Feb 2021 15:52:51 -0400","score":3,"shortened date":"14\/02\/2021 15:52:51","questions":[{"number":1,"question":"What is the two-day seminar that is held in conjunction with the National Leadership Conference by FBLA?","answer":["Institute for Leaders"],"correct":"true","user answer":["Institute for Leaders"]},{"number":2,"question":"For competitive events in which it is required, according to the FBLA Format Guide, which of the following are acceptable fonts?","answer":["Arial","Calibri","Times New Roman"],"correct":"true","user answer":["Arial","Times New Roman","Calibri"]},{"number":3,"question":"In which U.S. state was the first FBLA state chapter established?","answer":["Iowa"],"correct":"true","user answer":["iowa"]},{"number":4,"question":"Match the following officer roles to their responsibilities in FBLA","answer":["President : preside over all meetings","Secretary : keep an accurate membership and attendance roll","Treasurer : receive and act as custodian of chapter funds"],"correct":"true","user answer":["President : preside over all meetings","Secretary : keep an accurate membership and attendance roll","Treasurer : receive and act as custodian of chapter funds"]},{"number":5,"question":"FBLA has an international presence in Vietnam.","answer":["false"],"correct":"true","user answer":["false"]}],"time":21},{"date":"Sat, 13 Feb 2021 20:02:26 -0400","score":1,"shortened date":"13\/02\/2021 20:02:26","questions":[{"number":1,"question":"What does FBLA stand for?","answer":["Future Business Leaders of America"],"correct":"false","user answer":["First Bureau of Leadership Astuteness"]},{"number":2,"question":"Match the following levels of the FBLA Business Achievement Awards to when they would be presented to their respective winners","answer":["Future : Presented at a local awards ceremony or FBLA event by advisor","Leader : Presented at State Leadership Conference","America : Presented at National Leadership Conference"],"correct":"false","user answer":["Future : No answer","Leader : No answer","America : No answer"]},{"number":3,"question":"What is the minimum number of members required for an FBLA chapter?","answer":["5"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":4,"question":"The PBL part of FBLA-PBL is an acronym representing Greek letters.","answer":["true"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":5,"question":"Which of the following are NOT official FBLA fundraising partners?","answer":["Chipotle","Sam\u2019s Club","Baja Fresh"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]}],"time":3},{"date":"Sat, 13 Feb 2021 20:00:19 -0400","score":1,"shortened date":"13\/02\/2021 20:00:19","questions":[{"number":1,"question":"Which of the following are NOT levels of the FBLA Business Achievement Awards?","answer":["Entrepreneur","Pioneer"],"correct":"false","user answer":["Business"]},{"number":2,"question":"Match the following scholarships FBLA helps to offer with their respective winnings","answer":["FBLA Distinguished Business Leader Scholarship : $500 per winner","Johnson & Wales University Scholarship : up to full tuition for winners","National Technical Honor Society Scholarship : $1,000 per winner"],"correct":"false","user answer":["FBLA Distinguished Business Leader Scholarship : No answer","Johnson & Wales University Scholarship : No answer","National Technical Honor Society Scholarship : No answer"]},{"number":3,"question":"What is the membership theme of FBLA for the 2020-2021 year?","answer":["aspire"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":4,"question":"Where was the concept of FBLA developed?","answer":["Columbia University"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":5,"question":"FBLA sells bow ties as a part of its official merchandise.","answer":["true"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]}],"time":3},{"date":"Sat, 13 Feb 2021 19:56:12 -0400","score":1,"shortened date":"13\/02\/2021 19:56:12","questions":[{"number":1,"question":"What is the membership theme of FBLA for the 2020-2021 year?","answer":["aspire"],"correct":"true","user answer":["aspire"]},{"number":2,"question":"Who is credited as the founder of FBLA?","answer":["Hamden L. Forkner"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":3,"question":"Which of the following are objective tests in FBLA?","answer":["Business Communications","Sports & Entertainment Management","Personal Finance"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":4,"question":"Match the following FBLA Chapter programs to each of their respective focus","answer":["Super Sweeps : recruitment and retention","Non-Stop November : membership involvement","Action Awareness : FBLA awareness"],"correct":"false","user answer":["Super Sweeps : No answer","Non-Stop November : No answer","Action Awareness : No answer"]},{"number":5,"question":"FBLA has an international presence in Haiti.","answer":["true"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]}],"time":5},{"date":"Fri, 12 Feb 2021 20:02:04 -0400","score":2,"shortened date":"12\/02\/2021 20:02:04","questions":[{"number":1,"question":"FBLA sells bow ties as a part of its official merchandise.","answer":["true"],"correct":"true","user answer":["true"]},{"number":2,"question":"For competitive events in which it is required, according to the FBLA Format Guide, which of the following are acceptable fonts?","answer":["Arial","Calibri","Times New Roman"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":3,"question":"What is the first line of the FBLA Code of Ethics?","answer":["I will be honest and sincere"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":4,"question":"How many winners are there for the National Technical Honor Society Scholarship?","answer":["2"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":5,"question":"Match the following scholarships FBLA helps to offer with their respective winnings","answer":["FBLA Distinguished Business Leader Scholarship : $500 per winner","Johnson & Wales University Scholarship : up to full tuition for winners","National Technical Honor Society Scholarship : $1,000 per winner"],"correct":"false","user answer":["FBLA Distinguished Business Leader Scholarship : No answer","Johnson & Wales University Scholarship : No answer","National Technical Honor Society Scholarship : No answer"]}],"time":3},{"date":"Fri, 12 Feb 2021 18:31:58 -0400","score":1,"shortened date":"12\/02\/2021 18:31:58","questions":[{"number":1,"question":"Which of the following are NOT types of Competitive Events under FBLA?","answer":["Essay Writings","Performing Arts Events"],"correct":"false","user answer":["Demonstration Events"]},{"number":2,"question":"FBLA sells bow ties as a part of its official merchandise.","answer":["true"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":3,"question":"What does FBLA stand for?","answer":["Future Business Leaders of America"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":4,"question":"What is the membership theme of FBLA for the 2020-2021 year?","answer":["aspire"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":5,"question":"Match the following people to their importance within FBLA","answer":["Dorothy L. Travis : who the Parliamentary Procedure Event is named after","Hollis and Kitty Guy : who the Gold Seal Award of Merit is named after","Jean Buckley : former president of the national FBLA-PBL office"],"correct":"false","user answer":["Dorothy L. Travis : No answer","Hollis and Kitty Guy : No answer","Jean Buckley : No answer"]}],"time":3},{"date":"Sun, 14 Mar 2021 20:01:53 -0400","score":0,"shortened date":"14\/03\/2021 20:01:53","questions":[{"number":1,"question":"In which month, every year, is the National FBLA-PBL Week?","answer":["February"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":2,"question":"For competitive events in which it is required, according to the FBLA Format Guide, which of the following are acceptable fonts?","answer":["Arial","Calibri","Times New Roman"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":3,"question":"What is the two-day seminar that is held in conjunction with the National Leadership Conference by FBLA?","answer":["Institute for Leaders"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":4,"question":"Edward D. Miller was the first full-time executive director of FBLA-PBL.","answer":["true"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":5,"question":"Match the following dates to their importance","answer":["November 15 : American Enterprise Day","November 17 : March of Dimes World Prematurity Day","March 1 : Date by which dues must be received for competition eligibility"],"correct":"false","user answer":["November 15 : No answer","November 17 : No answer","March 1 : No answer"]}],"time":2},{"date":"Sun, 14 Mar 2021 20:01:47 -0400","score":1,"shortened date":"14\/03\/2021 20:01:47","questions":[{"number":1,"question":"Match the following scholarships FBLA helps to offer with their respective winnings","answer":["FBLA Distinguished Business Leader Scholarship : $500 per winner","Johnson & Wales University Scholarship : up to full tuition for winners","National Technical Honor Society Scholarship : $1,000 per winner"],"correct":"false","user answer":["FBLA Distinguished Business Leader Scholarship : No answer","Johnson & Wales University Scholarship : No answer","National Technical Honor Society Scholarship : No answer"]},{"number":2,"question":"Where is FBLA currently headquartered?","answer":["Reston, Virginia"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":3,"question":"Which of the following are objective tests in FBLA?","answer":["Business Communications","Sports & Entertainment Management","Personal Finance"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":4,"question":"A collared dress shirt with a necktie is acceptable attire for FBLA conferences.","answer":["true"],"correct":"true","user answer":["true"]},{"number":5,"question":"How many different articles are there in the FBLA Bylaws?","answer":["13"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]}],"time":4},{"date":"Sun, 14 Mar 2021 20:01:39 -0400","score":0,"shortened date":"14\/03\/2021 20:01:39","questions":[{"number":1,"question":"What was the Professional Division of FBLA originally called?","answer":["Alumni Division"],"correct":"false","user answer":["Business Sector"]},{"number":2,"question":"How many different articles are there in the FBLA Bylaws?","answer":["13"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":3,"question":"Jean Buckley is the current president of the FBLA national association.","answer":["false"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":4,"question":"Match the following FBLA Community Service Awards to their required number of hours","answer":["CSA Community : 50 hours","CSA Service : 200 hours","CSA Achievement : 500 hours"],"correct":"false","user answer":["CSA Community : No answer","CSA Service : No answer","CSA Achievement : No answer"]},{"number":5,"question":"Which of the following are the core activities on which all levels of the Business Achievement Awards are based off of, as outlined by FBLA?","answer":["Service","Education","Progress"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]}],"time":3},{"date":"Sun, 14 Mar 2021 20:01:05 -0400","score":0,"shortened date":"14\/03\/2021 20:01:05","questions":[{"number":1,"question":"Match the following people to their importance within FBLA","answer":["Dorothy L. Travis : who the Parliamentary Procedure Event is named after","Hollis and Kitty Guy : who the Gold Seal Award of Merit is named after","Jean Buckley : former president of the national FBLA-PBL office"],"correct":"false","user answer":["Dorothy L. Travis : No answer","Hollis and Kitty Guy : No answer","Jean Buckley : No answer"]},{"number":2,"question":"Which of the following are NOT official FBLA fundraising partners?","answer":["Chipotle","Sam\u2019s Club","Baja Fresh"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":3,"question":"FBLA has an international presence in Vietnam.","answer":["false"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":4,"question":"What Greek letter does the P in FBLA-PBL stand for?","answer":["phi"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]},{"number":5,"question":"In what year was the first high school FBLA chapter chartered?","answer":["1942"],"correct":"false","user answer":[""]}],"time":2}]